wbx.me 2010-12-11

# Mobile apps, web widgets, and rich media ads — Widgetbox

## Widgetbox Privacy Policy Statement

This site is owned and operated by Widgetbox, Inc. (“Widgetbox” or “We”). We understand you value your privacy. At Widgetbox, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe. This statement governs information you provide to us or we learn from your use of this web site and tells you how we may collect, use, and in some instances share this information.

INFORMATION WIDGETBOX COLLECTS

Widgetbox gathers two types of information about this website’s users:

  * Personal information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions, such as email, survey information, and online registration forms to Widgetbox. Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, your name, home address, company name, telephone number, e-mail address, and credit card information such as the credit card number, card verification value, and the billing address. The types and amount of personal information collected for these activities will vary depending on the activity.
  * Widgetbox also gathers non-personal information through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This non-personal information collected includes click-throughs, IP addresses, and usage data. This non-personal information allows us to better tailor our content to site users’ needs.

Usage Tracking

We track product usage data and user traffic patterns throughout our site to improve the content of our Web pages and the quality of our service. In addition, we track click-through information, including IP addresses, to our site from the reports and emails we sent to our customers. This is done to gauge the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns and to discourage fraudulent use.

COOKIES

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are required to use the Widgetbox service. We use cookies to record current session information. Additionally, if you choose the ‘remember me’ option, you are issued a permanent cookie. A permanent cookie is one that remains on the hard drive after the browser application has been closed.

Children

Consistent with the federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requiring parental consent. Any person who provides their personal information to Widgetbox through this web site represents that they are 13 years of age or older.

WIDGETBOX’S USE OF INFORMATION

We use the personal information about you stored in our member database in various ways. We use the personal information collected to provide you with our products and services. In addition, the personal information collected is used for identification and authentication, billing, and to contact you. Finally, information we gather may be used to otherwise improve our services.

WIDGETBOX’S TRANSFER AND INFORMATION SHARING POLICY

We do not share personal information collected on this web site with third parties for their direct marketing. We provide personal information to trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf.

Widgetbox does not otherwise share personal information about site users with third parties unless doing so is appropriate to carry out a user’s request or it reasonably believes that doing so is legally required or is in Widgetbox’s interest to protect its property or other legal rights or the rights or property of others.

If Widgetbox should ever file for bankruptcy or have its assets sold to or merge with another entity, information Widgetbox receives from you from this Site is a Widgetbox asset and may be transferred.

INTERNATIONAL VISITORS AND CUSTOMERS

This web site is hosted in the United States. If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States which does not have the same data protection laws as the EU and by providing your personal data you consent to:

  * the use of your personal data for the purposes identified above in accordance with this Privacy Policy; and
  * the transfer of your personal data to the United States as indicated above.

SECURITY

No data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure security on our systems. We use secure server software (SSL) and firewalls to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software.

If Widgetbox learns of a security systems breach we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using this web site or providing personal information to us you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy and administrative issues relating to your use of this site. Widgetbox may post a notice on our web site if a security breach occurs. If this happens, you will need a web browser enabling you to view the Widgetbox.com web site. Widgetbox may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us in these circumstances. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us at support@widgetbox.com.

CHANGES AND UPDATES

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the “last updated” date on the Privacy Policy. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are protecting the Personal Information we collect. Your continued use of this web site constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Statement and any updates.

CONTACTING WIDGETBOX

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please email us at support@widgetbox.com

Postal Mail Address:  
Widgetbox  
706 Mission Street  
Floor 5  
San Francisco, CA 94103  
Attention: Privacy Officer

[Last Updated: October 19, 2010]
